Guide to the Wells Rich Greene Inc. Records, 1954-1998 and undated RL.01365
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1954-1998 and undated (Acc. 98-0396), 140 boxes
  - Video and Film
    - BDDP (Box 126)
      - BDDP 8. McDonald's--McMorning. 1996. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126, Video-cassette BDDP 8, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0002, Video-file bddp_08.mov)
      - The Best of BDDP International Compilation Reel (list enclosed). 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126)
      - BDDP --BMW Airbag. 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126)
      - BDDP. WRG BDDP 1966-1996- 5 spots--Braniff; BC; Alka Seltzer; New York State; Oil of Olay. 1966-1996. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126)
      - BDDP Worldwide--Best of 1995-96 (list enclosed) BBL; Svobodne Slovo Newspaper; Dansk Supermarket; Caisse d'Epargne; BMW; Epson; Elf; McCain; LU; Aprilia; UAP; Stresstabs; Red Stripe; TV Licence; Third World Debt; Interflora; Onda Cero; Nenuco; Tendencias; Sogo; Ad Council; Clairol; Heineken; Miaville & LaGrand; McDonald's; Mercedes Benz; Sony; Medialite. 1995-1996. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126, Video-cassette BDDP Worldwide Best Of, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0002, Video-file bddp_worldwide_best_of_1995_1996.mov)
      - BDDP Worldwide--Best of 1995-1996-- [BDDP Worldwide Meeting Barcelona 1996 (BDDP Conseil) -- (list enclosed) same as above except VCR. 1995-1996. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126)
      - BDDP. BDDP Europe Reel (list enclosed) France--Tag Heuer, BMW, McDonald's, Beun, Caisse d'Epargne, UAP, Virgin; Italy--Aprilla; Spain--Nenuco, Onda Cero; Holland--Center Parcs; Singapore--Sony, Mercedes; Portugal--UAP; UK--Third World Debt, TV Licence; India--Haywards,. 1997. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126, Video-cassette BDDP Europe, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0002, Video-file bddp_europe_reel_082097.mov)
      - Wells Rich Greene BDDP, Inc Worldwide Meeting Cannes. 1997. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 126)
      - Rough Narration--Linda Kaplan Thaler. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. NT-VHS. (Box 126)
  - Audio Tapes
    - [Ad Council: see box 128] (Box 127)
      - unspecified (Box 127)
    - No information
      - B1-B67. 72 reels. Circa 1976-1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 127)
    - Ad Council (Box 128)
      - M36--M66. 7 reels--Drunk Driving Circa 14:00; Rawanda 1:40; Aids :45. 1990-1994. TRT: Circa 17:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 128)
      - M66A--M80. 5 reels--Drunk Driving4:30; Rawanda ?. Circa 1994-1995. TRT: Over 4:30. Audiocassette. (Box 128)
      - M66--M104. 2 reels--Drunk Driving 3:00;. 1994-1996. TRT: 2:00. DAT cassette. (Box 128)
    - Canada Dry & Sunkist
      - N1--N25. 19 reels Canada Dry reels. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 128)
      - N6--N16. 5 reels Sunkist reels. Undated. TRT: 15:30. Reel-to-reel. (Box 128)
    - Carmello Candy
      - O1--O3. 3 reels--3 spots. 1987-1988. TRT: 1:30. Reel-to-reel. (Box 128)
    - Catholic Church-- Special Job
      - M9--M10. 2 reels--7 spots. 1981. TRT: 3:30. Reel-to-reel. (Box 128)
    - [Chase Manhattan Bank: see box 129] (Box 128)
    - Citizens
      - 1 reel--2 spots (both Nothing Happened). 1996. TRT: 2:00. DAT cassette. (Box 128)
    - Clairol Herbal Essence
      - AA1-AA2. 2 reels--7 spots. 1995-1997. TRT: 4:45. Audiocassette. (Box 128)
    - [Continental Airlines: see box 129] (Box 128)
    - Dun & Bradstreet
      - M33--M62A. 8 reels--24 spots. 1992-1994. TRT: Circa 25:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 128)
    - Family Council
      - M8. 1 reel. 1977. TRT: :30. Reel-to-reel. (Box 128)
    - Folger's Coffee
      - R1-R2. 2 reel--2 spots. 1987. TRT: 2:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 128)
    - [Ford: see box 130] (Box 128)
    - Hush Puppies
      - M21-M32. 3 reels--5 spots. 1976-1980. TRT: 3:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 128)
    - Junior Achievement
      - M2-M7. 8 reels--11 spots. Circa 1976-1981. TRT: Circa 7:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 128)
    - Liberty Mutual
      - H2-H14 & 20 (also BB). 17 reels. 1985-. TRT: Not indicated. Reel-to-reel. (Box 128)
      - BB15-BB21. 5 reels--11 spots. 1995-1996. TRT: 7:30 plus. Audiocassette. (Box 128)
      - BB22. 1 reel. 1997. TRT: :30. DAT cassette. (Box 128)
    - Loehmann's
      - 1 reel--6 spots--Fall Fashions Previews. 1991. TRT: 6:00. Audiocassette. (Box 128)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 129)
      - Z1-Z57. 60 reels. 1991-1996. TRT: Not indicated. Reel-to-reel. (Box 129)
      - R1-R2. 2 reels--Circa 36 spots. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. Audiocassette. (Box 129)
      - Z43--Z55. 7 reels--11 spots. 1994-1996. TRT: Not indicated. Audiocassette. (Box 129)
      - Z-47 & Z58. 2 reel--2 spots. 1995-1996. TRT: Not indicated. DAT cassette. (Box 129)
    - Continental Airlines
      - W1-W7. 9 reels. 1990. TRT: Not indicated. Reel-to-reel. (Box 129)
    - Ford (Box 130)
      - A1-A68. 70 reels. 1979-1994. TRT: 145:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 130)
    - Continental Airlines (continued) (Box 131)
      - W8-W46. 42 reels. 1990-1993. TRT: Circa 86:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 131)
    - MCI
      - Q1-Q35. 37 reels. 1988-1989. TRT: Circa 62:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 131)
      - includes 7 copies of Q35 (divided in box) --Rocky. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 131)
      - includes 3 copies of Q35--Pride (Box 131)
    - MCI (Box 132)
      - Q35-Q68. 19 reels. 1989-1990. TRT: 77:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 132)
      - 1 reel--compilation reel of 28 spots. 1988. TRT: 28:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 132)
    - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center
      - M30-M31. 2 reels--4 spots. 1987. TRT: 3:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 132)
    - [Midas: see box 133] (Box 132)
    - Procter & Gamble
      - I16--I22. 3 reels--Gain Detergent--4 spots. 1986. TRT: 3:30. Reel-to-reel. (Box 132)
      - I19--I42. 6 reels--Oil of Olay--11 spots. 1988-1993. TRT: Not indicated. Reel-to-reel. (Box 132)
      - I1--I6. 4 reels--Prell--3 spots. 1981-1983. TRT: 1:30. Reel-to-reel. (Box 132)
      - I14--I39. 20 reels--Pringles--33 spots. 1985-1992. TRT: 26:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 132)
      - 12 reels--Sure--15 spots. 1982-1987. TRT: 10:45. Reel-to-reel. (Box 132)
      - I43. 1 reel--Pringles--3 spots. 1996. TRT: 3:00. DAT cassette. (Box 132)
    - Mobil Land
      - M79--M87. 2 reels--2 spots. 1995. TRT: 2:00. Audiocassette. (Box 132)
      - M97--M102. 2 reels--3 spots. 1996. TRT: Circa 3:00. DAT cassette. (Box 132)
    - Mobil Oil
      - G1-G4. 4 reels--4 spots (all Hefty/Wimpy). 1985. TRT: 4:00 (Box 132)
    - Midas (Box 133)
      - K1-K33. 43 reels--1 to 6 spots each (some duplication). 1977-1985. TRT: 110:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 133)
      - 12 reels--compilation reels (up to Circa 20:00 each); includes 3--1990 Availability Reel (A-C)--63 spots; also 4--1992 Availability Reel (A-D) 1990-1993. TRT: 40:00 plus 63:00; 53:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 133)
      - 32-track stereo reels--45 spots. Circa 1993. TRT: 43:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 133)
      - K4--K29. 19 reels--. 1993-1995. TRT: 165:00. Audiocassette. (Box 133)
      - K30-K31. 2 reels. 1995. TRT: 2:00. DAT cassette. (Box 133)
    - New York State (Box 134)
      - E1--E50. 51 reels--84 spots. 1977-1991. TRT: Circa 87:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 134)
    - New York Stock Exchange
      - M46--M95. 18 reels--44 spots. 1992-1995. TRT: 20:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 134)
      - M88--M94A. 2 Reels--1 spot and NYSE Buffet Interview. 1996. TRT: 1:00 plus. Audiocassette. (Box 134)
    - Off-Broadway
      - M71. Stiller & Meara. 1995. TRT: Not indicated. Audiocassette. (Box 134)
      - M72. Helen Hunter. 1995. TRT: Not indicated. Audiocassette. (Box 134)
      - M73. Sam Waterson. 1995. TRT: Not indicated. Audiocassette. (Box 134)
      - M74. Ruby Dee & Ossie Davis. 1995. TRT: Not indicated. Audiocassette. (Box 134)
      - M98. Rita Moreno. 1996. TRT: Not indicated. Audiocassette. (Box 134)
      - M7. Rita Moreno. 1996. TRT: Not indicated. DAT cassette. (Box 134)
    - Pan American World Airways (Box 135)
      - D1-D80. 80 reels--80 spots--. 1982-1984. TRT: 78:30. Reel-to-reel. (Box 135)
    - Pan American World Airways (continued) (Box 136)
      - D81-D162. 86 spots. 1984-1988. TRT: 86:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 136)
      - 2 reels--3 spots. 1983-1988. TRT: 3:00. Audiocassette. (Box 136)
    - Police Athletic League (Box 137)
      - M-37 & M38. 2 reels (both Body and Mind). 1991. TRT: 2:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 137)
    - Ralston Purina
      - M24-M25. 2 reels--2 spots for Chex Party Mix. Undated. TRT: 1:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 137)
      - M26. 1 reel--1 spot--Great American Dog Food. Undated. TRT: Circa :30. Reel-to-reel. (Box 137)
      - P-1. 1 reel--Bran Chex Brand Cereal--Confessions. 1988. TRT: 1:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 137)
    - Savin
      - L13-L14. 2 reels--2 spots. 1983-1984. TRT: 1:50 (Box 137)
    - Seagrams
      - X1--X35. 43 reels--89 spots (some duplication). 1990-1995. TRT: Circa 81:40. Reel-to-reel. (Box 137)
      - M32. 2 reels--1 spots. 1989. TRT: Circa 1:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 137)
      - X32. 1 travel case--16 spots. 1995. TRT: 14:40. Reel-to-reel. (Box 137)
      - X17--35. 8 reels--39 spots plus Master. 1993-1995 (Box 137)
      - MCI 1 Video Reels (Box 137)
      - 2 reels--Historical Reels--54 spots. 1988 & 1990. TRT: Not indicated. 1" video reel. (Box 137)
    - Sunoco (Box 138)
      - J1-J56. 63 reels--182 spots. 1977-1986. TRT: Circa 148:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 138)
      - J78-J88. 11 reels--11 spots. 1986-1987. TRT: 9:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 138)
    - Sunoco (continued) (Box 139)
      - J89-J127. 46 reels--108 spots. 1987-1992. TRT: 42:30. Reel-to-reel. (Box 139)
      - . 6 reels--51 spots. 1986-1987. TRT: 53:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 139)
    - Summer Jobs
      - M11-M15. 5 reels--5 spots (all Summer Jobs) --2 in Spanish. 1983. TRT: 2:50. Reel-to-reel. (Box 139)
    - Toys'R'Us
      - CC2-CC9. 8 reels--12 spots. 1996-1997. TRT: 0.5. Audiocassette. (Box 139)
      - . 1 reel--2 spots. 1996. TRT: 1:53. DAT cassette (Box 139)
    - United Industries
      - M45. 1 reel--Hot Shot--1 spot--Get a life. 1992. TRT: :30. Reel-to-reel. (Box 139)
      - M49--M63. 3 reels--Rid-A-Bug--25 spots. 1992-1994. TRT: Circa 19:00. Reel-to-reel. (Box 139)
    - Warners Bra
      - M16-M20. 5 reels--5 spots. 1978-1984. TRT: 4:20. Reel-to-reel. (Box 139)
    - WRG Corporate--Sound Track--6 tracks
      - (W7-1). Music Tracks. 1990. TRT: Not indicated. 15 ips reel-to-reel. (Box 139)
      - Master Radio--1982 Historical Reel (no list). 1982. TRT: Not indicated. 3-3/4 ips reel-to-reel. (Box 139)
      - Master Radio 1983 (no list). 1983. TRT: Not indicated. 3-3/4 ips reel-to-reel. (Box 139)
      - 3 reels--Mary Calhoon Moss Presentation Feb. 25, 1986. 1986. TRT: Not indicated. Reel-to-reel. (Box 139)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 140)
      - 3 reels--Mary Calhoon Presents: The Real Story:. 1986. TRT: 15:00 (5:00 each). 1" Video Reels (Box 140)
      - 2 reels--Comp Art. 1986. TRT: Not indicated. 1" Video Reels (Box 140)
      - 1 reel--Bump Up Material. 1986. TRT: Not indicated. 1" Video Reels (Box 140)
      - 1 reel--Embossed Logo Treatment with Fade. 1992. TRT: Not indicated. 1" Video Reels (Box 140)
      - 9 reels--Ad Council--Drunk Driving--24 spots (some Spanish). Circa 1992-1993. TRT: 9:25. 1" Video Reels (Box 140)
      - 3 MCI--323 Spots (see 136). 1988-1991. TRT: Not indicated. 1" Video Reels (Box 140)